- Yes!
- 是的！
Bring back the art of letter writing.
找回书信写作的艺术。
I'm so excited to open these up.
我太兴奋能拆开这些信了。
Oh, this person's been to the fountain. Here we go.
噢，这个人去过那个喷泉。 我们要开始了。
Oh, Agence Grateau paper. Where did you get this stationery?
噢，Agence Grateau 的信纸。 你从哪里弄到这套信具的？
I want some of that. I don't even have that.
我也想要一些。 我甚至都没有。
Wow.
哇。
"Dear Lily, I'm writing you a letter I probably should
“亲爱的 Lily，我正在给你写一封
have sent a long time ago.
我可能很久以前就该寄出的信。”
Perhaps I needed to find both the courage
“也许我需要先找到勇气
and the perfect stationery first."
和完美的信纸。”
You nailed it.
你做到了。
"'Emily in Paris' came into my life
“《艾米丽在巴黎》进入我的生活
at a very particular moment.
是在一个非常特殊的时刻。”
It was right after the lockdown,
“那是封锁刚结束的时候，”
and I had just started a new office job
“我刚开始一份新的办公室工作，”
where I felt lost, out of place, even invisible at times,
“在那里我感到迷茫、格格不入， 有时甚至觉得自己是透明的，”
and then came Emily.
“然后艾米丽出现了。”
Your Emily.
“你的艾米丽。”
She helped me face my own doubts professionally
“她帮我更有信心面对自己”
and personally with more confidence,
“在职业和个人方面的疑虑，”
and dare I say, more style.
“而且我敢说，还带了点风格。”
I've watched the show dozens of times.
“这部剧我看过几十次了。”
It became a colorful refuge.
“它成了一个色彩缤纷的避风港。”
Paris, boldness, friendship, dreams, and that magical way
“巴黎、大胆、友谊、梦想， 以及那种把每一次跌倒”
of turning every fall into a new kind of flight.
“化为一种新的飞翔的神奇方式。”
Thank you for your talent, your generosity,
“谢谢你的才华，你的慷慨，”
and bringing to life a character
“以及赋予这个角色生命，”
who helped me far more than you might imagine.
“她对我的帮助远超你的想象。”
With all my inspiration, Raph."
“带着我全部的灵感，Raph。”
I can't imagine what it would feel like, I know as Emily,
我无法想象那是什么感觉，我知道作为艾米丽（的感觉），
but actually taking the risk and moving somewhere foreign
但实际上像你一样冒险搬到异国他乡，
and taking a job like you did and succeeding.
找一份工作并取得成功。
So I'm very in awe of you,
所以我对你感到非常敬佩，
and I truly appreciate these words
我真的很感激这些话，
and the photo from the fountain.
还有那张喷泉的照片。
Aw, nice handwriting.
哇，笔迹真漂亮。
"Lily, this letter comes all the way from Brazil.
“Lily，这封信远道来自巴西。”
I know you have been here before,
“我知道你以前来过这里，”
and I hope you felt the warmth of our hearts.
“我希望你感受到了我们内心的温暖。”
You are such a powerful and honest actress.
“你是一位如此强大、诚实的演员。”
You truly deliver in every role you play,
“你演出的每一个角色都非常出色，”
but there's something magical about Emily.
“但艾米丽身上有一种神奇的特质。”
Thank you for giving life to such a bright, kind, funny,
“谢谢你赋予了艾米丽生命，”
and fearless character.
“这样一个阳光、善良、有趣且无畏的角色。”
She reminded me that being dreamy, delulu," love that word,
“她提醒我，喜欢幻想、‘delulu’，”我喜欢这个词，
"and yes, different, is not only okay, it is beautiful.
“是的，与众不同，不仅没关系，而且很美。”
With love from Brazil, Jean."
“来自巴西的爱，Jean。”
Being delulu is always okay.
保持一点幻想总是好的。
These are qualities in Emily that I really love myself,
艾米丽身上的这些品质也是我自己非常喜欢的，
and I try to aspire to have more of myself as Lily.
作为 Lily，我也尝试让自己拥有更多这样的特质。
So it's really kind of you to say that that comes through.
所以听到你这么说，我感到非常贴心。
"Dear Lily Collins,
“亲爱的 Lily Collins，”
I started watching 'Emily in Paris' when I was 10,
“我从 10 岁开始看《艾米丽在巴黎》，”
and I loved it so, so much,
“我非常非常喜欢它，”
and I love how the character you play is so confident.
“我喜欢你扮演的角色是如此自信。”
She even helped me learn how to be more confident.
“她甚至帮我学会了如何变得更自信。”
I'm so excited for Season 5,
“我很期待第五季，”
and I wanted to tell you that you are so gorgeous,
“我想告诉你你真的很漂亮，”
and that your baby is adorable.
“还有你的宝宝非常可爱。”
I hope you have so much fun filming 'Emily in Paris.'
“我希望你拍摄《艾米丽在巴黎》很愉快。”
You're amazing. Love, Johanna S."
“你很棒。爱你的，Johanna S。”
Thank you, Johanna. You should always be confident.
谢谢你，Johanna。你应该永远保持自信。
I've looked up to many other women
我也仰望过许多其他女性，
who made me feel confident,
她们让我感到自信，
so this is a really lovely thing to say.
所以听到你这么说真的很棒。
So thank you.
谢谢。
And yes, my baby's adorable. Thank you.
是的，我的宝宝很可爱。谢谢。
"My name is Vafa,
“我叫 Vafa，”
and I'm writing you all the way from Azerbaijan
“我正从远在阿塞拜疆的地方给你写信，”
with a heart full of admiration and warmth.
“满怀着钦佩与温暖。”
I've watched 'Emily in Paris' not just once,
“《艾米丽在巴黎》我不只看了一次，”
but again and again, not only for the fashion and romance,
“而是一看再看，不仅是为了时尚和浪漫，”
but for you, the energy, sincerity,
更是为了你带来的活力、真诚
and grace you bring to the screen.
和你在银幕上展现出的优雅。
You inspire me to dream bigger, smile more,
“你激励我敢于梦想，多微笑，”
and embrace who I am.
“并拥抱真实的自我。”
Your kindness, elegance,
“你的善良、优雅和力量”
and strength shine through everything you do.
“体现在你所做的每一件事中。”
I just wanted to say thank you for being real,
“我只想说声谢谢，谢谢你的真实，”
for making us feel seen,
“谢谢你让我们感到被看见，”
and for sharing your light with the world.
“谢谢你向世界分享你的光芒。”
Sending you love and sunshine, Vafa."
“送给你爱与阳光，Vafa。”
You should always dream bigger,
你应该永远敢于梦想，
and I need to remind myself of that myself.
我自己也需要经常这样提醒自己。
So playing Emily certainly does that for me,
扮演艾米丽确实让我做到了这一点，
and reading letters like this.
读到这样的信也是如此。
Thank you so much to everyone who wrote in.
非常感谢每一位来信的人。
Your kind words and support mean so much to me.
你们亲切的话语和支持对我来说意义重大。
Truly, I'm very, very touched.
真的，我深受感动。
You can watch "Emily in Paris" Season 5 now on Netflix.
现在可以在 Netflix 上观看《艾米丽在巴黎》第五季。